yliving.com 2011-11-25

# YLiving Privacy Policy & Customer's Privacy Policy at YLiving.com

YLiving values its customers and respects their privacy. When you order, we need to know your name, email address, credit card billing address, mailing address, telephone number, credit card number, and credit card expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. By shopping with us, you agree that we may use your information for our own marketing purposes.

We use the latest encryption technology to keep your personal information safe. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to ensure the security of your online order information. To check the security of your connection, look at the lower left-hand corner of your browser window after you access our secure server (when you proceed to checkout). If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending upon your browser), then SSL is active. To double-check for security, look at the URL line of your browser. If you have accessed a secure server, the first characters of the site's address should change from "http" to "https." All your ordering information -- including your name, address, and credit card number -- is encrypted using a secure server for maximum security. Your credit card and billing information cannot be read as it travels to our ordering system.

Credit card transactions are handled by a respected third-party financial institution, which receives the credit card number and other personal identifying information only to verify the credit card numbers and process transactions.

Both YLiving and our hosting provider, Yahoo!, may set and access cookies on your computer to improve your shopping experience. You can configure your web browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set.

By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by YLiving. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

 _This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the[Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information._
